<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ACM Multimedia Asia 2022</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/</link><description>Recent content on ACM Multimedia Asia 2022</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mmasia2022.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Annoucement of Accepted Workshop: Multimedia Understanding with Pre-trained Models</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/07/11/multimedia-understanding-with-pre-trained-models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/07/11/multimedia-understanding-with-pre-trained-models/</guid><description>One of our workshops, Multimedia Understanding with Pre-trained Models, published the website!
http://staff.ustc.edu.cn/~zhwg/MMAsia_2022_workshop/index.html
Be patient for further details!</description></item><item><title>Call for Regular/Short Papers Released</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/19/release_cfp/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/19/release_cfp/</guid><description>We released Call for Regular Papers and Call for Short Papers.
We appreciate your consideration of submitting your research work to ACM Multimedia Asia 2022!</description></item><item><title>Call for Demo Papers Released</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/07/release_cfd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/07/release_cfd/</guid><description>We released Call for Demo Papers. The notification date was also updated to Sep. 23, 2022.
We appreciate your consideration of submitting your live and interactive demos to ACM Multimedia Asia 2022!</description></item><item><title>Call for Tutorials Released</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/07/release_cft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/07/release_cft/</guid><description>We released Call for Tutorials.
We welcome your tutorial proposals to reinforce the conference program!</description></item><item><title>Call for Workshop Proposals Released</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/07/release_cfwp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2022/06/07/release_cfwp/</guid><description>We released Call for Workshop Proposals and updated Important Dates.
The new deadline for workshop proposals is now June 30, 2022.
We are waiting for your proposals!</description></item><item><title>Important dates are available</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2021/01/15/important-dates-available/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2021/01/15/important-dates-available/</guid><description>Important dates are now available here. Put it on your calendar!</description></item><item><title>ACM MM Asia Site Open</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2021/01/07/categories-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/blog/2021/01/07/categories-post/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the launch of ACM Multimedia Asia 2022 website! More information will be added soon.</description></item><item><title>Call for Demo Papers</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_demo_papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_demo_papers/</guid><description>Overview ACM Multimedia Asia is a major annual international conference to showcase the scientific achievements and industrial innovations in the multimedia field. Multimedia research focuses on technologies that enable the use and exchange of content, integrating multiple perspectives of digital modalities, including images, text, video, audio (speech, music, etc.), and other sensor data.
ACM Multimedia Asia 2022 will provide demonstration sessions. Demos are intended as live and interactive proof of the presenters' research ideas and technological contributions to provide multimedia researchers and practitioners the opportunity to showcase working multimedia systems, applications, prototypes, or proofs-of-concept.</description></item><item><title>Call for Regular Papers</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_regular_papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_regular_papers/</guid><description>Overview ACM Multimedia Asia 2022 invites submission of research papers presenting novel theoretical and algorithmic solutions addressing problems across the domain of multimedia and related applications. The conference also encourages visionary papers on new and emerging topics; papers presenting novel ideas with promising (preliminary) results in realizing these ideas; application-oriented papers that make innovative technical contributions to social good, healthcare, etc. The topics of interest include but are not limited to:</description></item><item><title>Call for Short Papers</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_short_papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_short_papers/</guid><description>Overview Multimedia research focuses on technologies that enable the use and exchange of content integrating multiple perspectives of digital modalities, including images, text, video, audio (speech, music etc.), and other sensor data. ACM Multimedia Asia 2022 calls for short research papers presenting novel theoretical and algorithmic solutions addressing problems across the domain of multimedia and related applications. The conference also calls for short papers presenting novel ideas and promising (preliminary) results in realizing these ideas.</description></item><item><title>Call for Tutorials</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_tutorials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_tutorials/</guid><description>We are soliciting proposals for tutorials to be held in conjunction with the ACM Multimedia Asia 2022. The tutorials should aim to give a comprehensive review of a specific topic related to multimedia. The topic should be of sufficient relevance and importance to attract significant interest from the multimedia community. Typical tutorial audiences consist of graduate students, researchers and practitioners from both academia and industry. We mainly invite proposals for half-day (2-4 hours including breaks) tutorials.</description></item><item><title>Call for Workhop Papers</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_workshop_papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_workshop_papers/</guid><description>List of workshops: Multimedia Understanding with Pre-trained Models Multimedia Understanding with Pre-trained Models http://staff.ustc.edu.cn/~zhwg/MMAsia_2022_workshop/index.html
Overview Multi-modal understanding plays a crucial role in enabling the machine to perceive the physical world with multiple sensor cues as humans. Recently, large-scale pre-trained models (PTMs) has become a research hotspot in the field of artificial intelligence. Existing techniques follow the self-supervised learning paradigm achieve great success on the uni-modal scenes, such as computer vision (CV) and natural language process (NLP).</description></item><item><title>Call for Workhop Proposals</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_workshop_proposals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/call_for_workshop_proposals/</guid><description>Submission -- We are soliciting proposals for workshops to be held in conjunction with the ACM Multimedia Asia 2022 conference. The purpose of the workshop is to provide a comprehensive forum on current and emerging topics that could not be fully explored during the main conference and to encourage in-depth discussions of technical and application issues.
Proposal Format Each workshop proposal (maximum 4 pages in PDF format) must include:</description></item><item><title>Important Dates</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/important_dates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/important_dates/</guid><description> Submission deadline is at 11:59pm (AoE) of the stated deadline date. Workshop Proposals Submission June 30, 2022 Workshop Proposals Notification July 7, 2022 Regular/Short Papers (Full Track) Submission July 22, 2022 Demo Papers Submission August 19, 2022 Tutorial Proposals Submission August 26, 2022 Regular/Short Papers (Full Track) Notification September 16, 2022 Demo Papers Notification September 23, 2022 Tutorial Proposals Notification September 16, 2022 Workshop Papers Notification September 30, 2022 Last update: June 8, 2022 &amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Organizers</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/organizers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/organizers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Program</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/program/</guid><description>Program -- To be announced.</description></item><item><title>Sponsors</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/sponsors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/sponsors/</guid><description>Sponsors -- To be announced.</description></item><item><title>Submission</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/submission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/submission/</guid><description>Submission -- To be announced.</description></item><item><title>Venue</title><link>https://www.mmasia2022.org/venue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mmasia2022.org/venue/</guid><description>ACM Multimedia Asia 2022 will be a hybrid conference with both in-person and online attendance options.
We will release the information on online attendance soon.
Yayoi Auditorium The conference will be held in Tokyo, the safest, most attractive, and most convenient city located in Japan. Our venue, the Yayoi Auditorium at The University of Tokyo, is in the heart of the city and is easily reachable from all over the world.</description></item></channel></rss>